sumopaint.com 2011-12-31

# Sumo Paint | Online Image Editor

| | 

### Esta política de privacidad describe cómo utilizamos y protegemos tu información personal.  
  
---|---  
  
## September 30, 2009

Please read this policy to understand what information Snap collects and how we use it. This policy concern all Sumo websites, products, services and third parties. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following address: Privacy Policy, Snap Group Ltd., PL 950, 00101 Helsinki, Finland or via email at info@sumo.fi. You can also send feedback from our site. 

## Information We Collect and How We Use it

When you register with Sumo account, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your username, e-mail address and the password for the account. We use this personal information to communicate with you, to inform and take contact with you. The information may also be used in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding unauthorized use of the services. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

We also collect anonymous, non-personal information, such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, your browser’s language, your web request and the date and time of your request. Such information does not identify you individually. Non-personal information can be used, for example, in marketing, auditing, to provide or to improve our services and also to develop new services. 

We also use "cookies" to collect information. When you visit the portal, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. It helps, for example, the service to recognize your saved documents. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

## Information Sharing

Except as noted below, Snap does not share your personal information with third parties unless you give us your permission. Snap only shares personal information with third parties in the following circumstances: 

  * We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this policy; 
  * In order to provide products or services you have requested; 
  * There are other instances in which Snap may divulge your personal information, such as when required by law, regulation, or litigation. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. 

If Snap becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Snap may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. 

## Information Security

Snap takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Snap employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

## Other

Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent. If we make any material changes to our policy, we will post a new policy on our site and update the "last updated" date set forth above. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account. Each version of this policy will be filed and we will also keep prior versions of this privacy policy in this website. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or if you have to change personal information, please feel free to contact us through this site or at the following address: 

Privacy Policy Snap Group Ltd  
PL 950  
00101 Helsinki 

|   
---  
|  |   
| | 

### We'd love to hear your thoughts and ideas

It will help us to serve you better! We would really like to hear any feedback about the Sumo site, the good, the bad, the ugly - bring it on! 

### Snap Group Ltd

PL 950, 00101 Helsinki, Finland  
mobile: +358 44 2738311  
email: info@sumo.fi  |   
---|---|---  
|  |
